automate.io 2018-11-23

# Privacy Policy

_Last modified: 18th June 2018_

Automate IO Inc. (formerly FlowApp Automation Inc.) (“Automate IO,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) provides an application integration platform and related services (“Services”). This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") details Automate IO’s policies and practices regarding its collection and use of your personal information and sets forth your privacy rights. 

###  Policy Scope and Links to Other Websites 

This Privacy Policy addresses activities on the Automate IO platform, altogether this website, and any other website or web-based system provided by Automate IO (the "Website"). Through the Website you are able to access links to other websites which are not under the control of Automate IO. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. This Privacy Policy does not cover the links within the Website that link to such other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you may visit. 

###  The Information We Collect and How We Use It 

###  To Provide the Automate IO Platform 

Automate IO collects personal information about you in order to: 

  1. identify you each time you visit our Website or wish to have a Service provided; 
  2. process orders or applications submitted by you; 
  3. improve our Services and Website; 
  4. customize your experience; 
  5. carry out research on the demographics, interests and behavior of our customers; 
  6. and send you information we think you may find useful, including information about how to effectively use our Services and new Automate IO products and Services. 

Depending on the Service, personal information we collect may include: 

  * first name; 
  * last name; 
  * email address; 
  * credit card number; and 
  * billing address. 

For Automate IO’s email communication purposes, the bases for lawful processing are: 

  1. to the extent that you have given us consent; 
  2. as necessary for the performance of a contract; or 
  3. for the purposes of pursuing Automate IO’s legitimate interest. 

###  Aggregated Service Data 

In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve Automate IO’s customers, at times Automate IO conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the personal information and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis and Automate IO may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents, and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally and is not considered to be personal information 

###  Through the Automate IO Website 

As is true of most other websites, the Website collects certain information automatically and stores it in log files. The information may include (i) internet protocol (“IP”) addresses, (ii) the region or general location where your computer or device is accessing the internet, (iii) browser and system information, and (iv) other actions performed by you on the Website. We use this information to help us design our Website to better suit our users’ needs. We may also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Website, analyze trends, track visitor movements, and gather broad demographic information that assists us in identifying visitor preferences. We do not link IP addresses to your name or email address. 

The Website also uses cookies. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. If you prefer, you may change your browser’s settings so that it will not automatically accept cookies. If you set your browser’s settings to block cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of the Website. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the internet. While cookies do identify a user’s computer, they do not personally identify customers or passwords. 

###  Third-Party Service Credentials 

Our Service allows you to integrate and create commands for various online third-party services ("Third-Party Services"). In order to take advantage of this feature, you may need to authenticate, register for or log into Third-Party Services through the Service or on the websites of their respective providers. When you enable linking between Third-Party Services through the Service, we collect relevant information necessary to enable the Service to access that Third-Party Service and your data and content contained within that Third-Party Service ("Login Credentials"). We store your Login Credentials in an encrypted format. 

When you enable the Service to link content and data between Third-Party Services, the Third-Party Services will provide us with access to certain information that you may have provided to the Third-Party Services, and we will use, store and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, please remember that the manner in which Third-Party Services use, store, and disclose your information is governed by the policies of such Third-Party Services and Automate IO shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Third-Party Services that may be enabled within the Service. 

We may retain certain personal non-identifiable information related to the data or content linked between Third-Party Services (for example, account information, recent data sent or received, link configuration, and names of the Third-Party Services), for the purpose of improving our Services. 

###  When and How We Share Information with Others 

We share personal information with third parties who are facilitating the delivery of Services. We may share our data, including personal information about you with our partners and joint ventures in furtherance of our business. Our partners and joint ventures follow privacy practices no less protective of all users than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Automate IO, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Automate IO goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that may be transferred to or acquired by a third party. 

Automate IO cooperates with law enforcement inquiries. Therefore, in response to a lawful request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your personal information. 

###  Individual Rights 

You may opt out of any future contact or notifications from us, change your notification preferences, or make any of the following requests at the contact information provided below: 

  * see what data we have about you, if any; 
  * change or correct any data we have about you; 
  * have us delete any data we have about you; and/or 
  * express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

###  Your Choices About Your Information 

You can contact us directly at [contact@automate.io](mailto:contact@automate.io) to review, correct, and delete the information about you that Automate IO keeps on file, or to change your notification preferences. 

###  Security of Your Information 

We maintain physical, technical and administrative safeguards to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the Website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data and Login Credentials), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Website. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. The computers/servers in which we store personal information and encrypted Login Credentials are kept in a secure environment. Only employees who need access to the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personal information. In addition, we commit to taking appropriate disciplinary measures to enforce our employees' privacy responsibilities. 

###  Compromise of Personal Information 

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Automate IO will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy and as required by Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the Processing of Personal Data and on the free movement of such data and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation) or other applicable law. 

###  Children 

Automate IO does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through the Services. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to Automate IO through the Services, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases. 

###  Notification Procedures 

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business-related purposes, to you by (i) email notice, (ii) written or hard copy notice, or (iii) through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Website, as determined by Automate IO in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy. 

###  Changes and Updates to the Privacy Policy 

Automate IO reserves the right to amend the Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason, without notice to you, other than the posting of the amended Privacy Policy on this Website. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. When we change the policy in a material manner we will let you know by updating the “Effective Date” at the top of this page. 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy please contact: 

**Automate IO Inc.**   
101 California St, Suite 2710   
San Francisco, CA, 94111 USA   
Email: [contact@automate.io](mailto:contact@automate.io)
